# **IMRAN ALI**





## **About Me**



Experienced 17/07/1989 Guna, Madhya Pradesh



Aim to be associated with progressive organization that gives example scope to apply my skills, knowledge and to involve myself as part of team that will work dynamically towards the growth of organization.



### **Education**

**High School** 

M.P Board, Bhopal Guna, Madhya Pradesh

Completed, March 2009

Intermediate

M.P Board, Bhopal Guna, Madhya Pradesh

Completed, March 2015

Bachelor of Commerce, WITH COMPUTER

MMVYY, JABALPUR (M.P) Guna, Madhya Pradesh

Completed, April 2019



## **Work Experience**



July 2008 - April 2012

#### **COSTUMER CARE OFFICER**

Wynncom Mobile+ Maxx Mobile INDIA PVT. LTD. Guna, Madhya Pradesh



July 2012 - March 2014

### **COSTUMER CARE OFFICER**

L.G INDIA PVT. LTD. Guna, Madhya Pradesh



November 2015 - Fabruary 2020

#### **DIGITAL SALES SPECIALIST**

RELIANCE JIO INFOCOM INDIA PVT. LTD.

Guna, Madhya Pradesh



#### **SALES EXECUTIVE**

VIVO INDIA PVT. LTD.

Guna, Madhya Pradesh



## **Skills**

#### Confident.

Good communication skills.

Leadership quality.

Multi-tasking & liaison abilities.

Self-motivated and positive attitude

Pro-activeness & I can do "attitude"



## **Computer Proficiency**

### **Operating Systems**

- Windows 7 • • •
- Windows XP ●●●
- Windows ME
  ● ●
- Windows 98
- Windows 95 ● ●
- Windows3.1 ••••

#### Software

- M.S-Office ●●●
- M.S-Excel ●●●
- M.S-Word
  ● ●
- M.S-Powerpoint
  ● ●
- M.S-Fontpage
- Computer Coral 5
- Computer organization
- Paintbrush
  ● ●
- English Typing ●●●●



## Languages

- Hindi
  ● ●
- English ●●●



Cricket Travelling Listning music watching movies communicating with people



## **Personal**

Father's Name: Mr. Shakir Ali Birthday: 17/07/1989 Marital Status: Nationality: Married Indian

Gender: Male

Address: Binova Bhave Ward no.23 B.G Road Guna.

Guna - 473001 Madhya Pradesh

India

### **Declaration**

I, Imran Ali, hereby declare that the information contained herein is true and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.

\$A.

Guna, Madhya Pradesh

**Imran Ali**